const questions = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question : "What was Charlie Parker's (Jazz musician) nickname?",
        answer: 'B. Bird',
        options: [
            "A. Magician",
            "B. Bird",
            "C. Solist",
            "D. God",
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 2,
        question : 'Who is Dali?',
        answer: 'B. Goddes of hunt',
        options: [
            "A. Goddes of rain",
            "B. Goddes of hunt",
            "C. Goddes of war",
            "D. My neighbour",
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 3,
        question : '"When the child was a child, it did not know, that it was a child..." Which movie starts with this quote?',
        answer: 'A. Wings of desire',
        options: [
            "A. Wings of desire",
            "B. Children of Men",
            "C. K-pax",
            "D. V for Vendetta",
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 4,
        question : '"All we are is dust in the wind" which rock band sang this lyrics?',
        answer: 'D. Kansas',
        options: [
            "A. Pink Floyd",
            "B. Metallica",
            "C. Scorpion",
            "D. Kansas"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 5,
        question : 'Which creature has three heads?',
        answer: 'A. Cerber',
        options: [
            "A. Cerber",
            "B. Basilisk",
            "C. Centaur",
            "D. Griffin"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        question : 'According to legend, who brought chocolate in Europe?',
        answer: 'C. Hernan Cortes',
        options: [
            "A. Ferdinand Magellan",
            "B. Vasco da Gama",
            "C. Hernan Cortes",
            "D. John Cabot"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 7,
        question : 'Who hols a record for being the oldest active football player?',
        answer: 'A. Miura Kazuyoshi',
        options: [
            "A. Miura Kazuyoshi",
            "B. Gianluigi Buffon",
            "C. Endō Yasuhito",
            "D. Joaquín Sánchez"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 8,
        question : 'Which pharaoh was called Ozymandias by ancient Greeks?',
        answer: 'B. Ramses II',
        options: [
            "A. Ramses I",
            "B. Ramses II",
            "C. Ramses III",
            "D. Ramses IV"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 9,
        question : `Which company owns "Assassin's creed"?`,
        answer: 'D. Ubisoft',
        options: [
            "A. EA",
            "B. Nintendo",
            "C. Sony",
            "D. Ubisoft"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 10,
        question : 'What was a stage name of Rafael Padilla, the first black clown to play a lead role in a circus pantomime act?',
        answer: 'C. Chocolat',
        options: [
            "A. African",
            "B. Black Raffaelo",
            "C. Chocolat",
            "D. Django"
        ]
    },
]